Finding Aid for Soundings Records 1977-1998
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Audiovisual
  - Videotapes
    - "Clips for video Soundings: A Center for Women," February 1994 (Box 6)
      (includes brief oral history interviews with executive director Lin Orrin and founder Gerry Brown)
    - WFIP, Dr. Marilyn Nagy: Women's Financial Independence Program undated (Box 6)
  - Photographs
    The Photographs sub-subseries, arranged chronologically, consists of an assortment of photographs taken throughout the decades of Soundings' existence. These photographs cover many occasions and situations, such as fundraising benefits, participant graduation ceremonies, and staff portraits, as well as other events and topically-themed photos for the newsletter. Many of these photographs are not well-documented as to subject matter or date. Included in the Photographs sub-subseries are photographs and memorabilia (programs and announcements) from the "Target Photo Album," which was disassembled for preservation reasons.
    - Target Photo Album circa 1978-1994, 2 folders (Box 6)
      (includes programs and flyers)
    - Soundings' 10th Anniversary 1988 (Box 6)
      (forms part of the Soundings' 10th Anniversary file in the Background series, Box 1)
    - 1989 (Box 6)
      (appears to include earlier and later photographs as well; original notes on envelope read "Christmas Party at Gerry's, Office on First Street, At Legnn's? [sic?], Party for the Board?, Mary Joscelyn?"; additional envelope labeled "Bach School," also 1989)
    - Open House October 20, 1989 (Box 6)
    - Soundings Breakfast Briefing June 1990 (Box 6)
      (forms part of the Soundings Breakfast Briefing file in the Grants series, Box 4)
    - Major Donor Thank You February 1991, includes negatives (Box 6)
      (forms part of the Major Donor Thank You file in the Grants series, Box 4)
    - Staff Photographs 1992, undated, includes negatives and one slide (Box 6)
    - Newsletter Pictures: from the Winter newsletters 1991, 1994 (Box 6)
      (1991 includes shots of Gerry Brown, Target participants, and board members)
    - Photographs: staff and Target participants circa 1996, includes negatives (Box 6)
  - Slides
    The Slides sub-subseries is arranged chronologically and like the photographs sub-subseries documents many occasions and situations, such as fundraising benefits, participant graduation ceremonies, and staff portraits.
    - Past Participants and Volunteers March 1992 (Box 6)
    - Target Reunion 1993 (Box 6)
    - Soundings Slide Show 1994 (Box 6)
      (related to "Soundings' Slide Show" sound recording)
    - Spring 1994 (Box 6)